<resources>
    <string name="app_name">LOL Champions</string>
    <string name="title">League of Legends Champions</string>
    <string name="expand_image">See more or less information about champion</string>
    <string name="aatrox">Aatrox - The Darkin Blade</string>
    <string name="aatrox_sum">Once honored defenders of Shurima against the Void, Aatrox and his brethren would eventually become an even greater threat to Runeterra, and were defeated only by cunning mortal sorcery. But after centuries of imprisonment, Aatrox was the first to find freedom once more, corrupting and transforming those foolish enough to try and wield the magical weapon that contained his essence. Now, with stolen flesh, he walks Runeterra in a brutal approximation of his previous form, seeking an apocalyptic and long overdue vengeance.</string>
    <string name="akali">Akali - The Rouge Assassin</string>
    <string name="akali_sum">Abandoning the Kinkou Order and her title of the Fist of Shadow, Akali now strikes alone, ready to be the deadly weapon her people need. Though she holds onto all she learned from her master Shen, she has pledged to defend Ionia from its enemies, one kill at a time. Akali may strike in silence, but her message will be heard loud and clear: fear the assassin with no master\.</string>
    <string name="aphelios">Aphelios - The Weapon Of The Faithful</string>
    <string name="aphelios_sum">Emerging from moonlight\'s shadow with weapons drawn, Aphelios kills the enemies of his faith in brooding silence—speaking only through the certainty of his aim, and the firing of each gun. Though fueled by a poison that renders him mute, he is guided by his sister Alune. From her distant temple sanctuary, she pushes an arsenal of moonstone weapons into his hands. For as long as the moon shines overhead, Aphelios will never be alone.</string>
    <string name="caitlyn">Caitlyn - The Sheriff Of Piltover</string>
    <string name="caitlyn_sum">Renowned as its finest peacekeeper, Caitlyn is also Piltover\'s best shot at ridding the city of its elusive criminal elements. She is often paired with Vi, acting as a cool counterpoint to her partner\'s more impetuous nature. Even though she carries a one-of-a-kind hextech rifle, Caitlyn\'s most powerful weapon is her superior intellect, allowing her to lay elaborate traps for any lawbreakers foolish enough to operate in the City of Progress.</string>
    <string name="diana">Diana - Scorn Of The Moon</string>
    <string name="diana_sum">Bearing her crescent moonblade, Diana fights as a warrior of the Lunari—a faith all but quashed in the lands around Mount Targon. Clad in shimmering armor the color of winter snow at night, she is a living embodiment of the silver moon\'s power. Imbued with the essence of an Aspect from beyond Targon\'s towering summit, Diana is no longer wholly human, and struggles to understand her power and purpose in this world.</string>
    <string name="ezreal">Ezreal - The Prodigal Explorer</string>
    <string name="ezreal_sum">A dashing adventurer, unknowingly gifted in the magical arts, Ezreal raids long-lost catacombs, tangles with ancient curses, and overcomes seemingly impossible odds with ease. His courage and bravado knowing no bounds, he prefers to improvise his way out of any situation, relying partially on his wits, but mostly on his mystical Shuriman gauntlet, which he uses to unleash devastating arcane blasts. One thing is for sure—whenever Ezreal is around, trouble isn\'t too far behind. Or ahead. Probably everywhere.</string>
    <string name="garen">Garen - The Might Of Demacia</string>
    <string name="garen_sum">A proud and noble warrior, Garen fights as one of the Dauntless Vanguard. He is popular among his fellows, and respected well enough by his enemies—not least as a scion of the prestigious Crownguard family, entrusted with defending Demacia and its ideals. Clad in magic-resistant armor and bearing a mighty broadsword, Garen stands ready to confront mages and sorcerers on the field of battle, in a veritable whirlwind of righteous steel.</string>
    <string name="ivern">Ivern - The Green Father</string>
    <string name="ivern_sum">Ivern Bramblefoot, known to many as the Green Father, is a peculiar half man, half tree who roams Runeterra\'s forests, cultivating life everywhere he goes. He knows the secrets of the natural world, and holds deep friendships with all things that grow, fly, and scuttle. Ivern wanders the wilderness, imparting strange wisdom to any he meets, enriching the forests, and occasionally entrusting loose-lipped butterflies with his secrets.</string>
    <string name="ksante">K\'Sante - The Pride Of Nazumah</string>
    <string name="ksante_sum">Defiant and courageous, K\'Sante battles colossal beasts and ruthless Ascended to protect his home of Nazumah, a coveted oasis amid the sands of Shurima. But after a falling-out with his former partner, K\'Sante realizes that in order to become a warrior worthy of leading his city, he must temper his single-minded drive for success. Only then can he avoid falling prey to his own pride and find the wisdom he needs to defeat the vicious monsters threatening his people.</string>
    <string name="neeko">Neeko - The Curious Chameleon</string>
    <string name="neeko_sum">Hailing from a long lost tribe of vastaya, Neeko can blend into any crowd by borrowing the appearances of others, even absorbing something of their emotional state to tell friend from foe in an instant. No one is ever sure where—or who—Neeko might be, but those who intend to do her harm will soon witness her true colors revealed, and feel the full power of her primordial spirit magic unleashed upon them.</string>
    <string name="ornn">Ornn - The Fire Below The Mountain</string>
    <string name="ornn_sum">Ornn is the Freljordian spirit of forging and craftsmanship. He works in the solitude of a massive smithy, hammered out from the lava caverns beneath the volcano Hearth-Home. There he stokes bubbling cauldrons of molten rock to purify ores and fashion items of unsurpassed quality. When other deities—especially Volibear—walk the earth and meddle in mortal affairs, Ornn arises to put these impetuous beings back in their place, either with his trusty hammer or the fiery power of the mountains themselves.</string>
    <string name="rakan">Rakan - The Charmer</string>
    <string name="rakan_sum">As mercurial as he is charming, Rakan is an infamous vastayan troublemaker and the greatest battle-dancer in Lhotlan tribal history. To the humans of the Ionian highlands, his name has long been synonymous with wild festivals, uncontrollable parties, and anarchic music. Few would suspect this energetic, traveling showman is also partner to the rebel Xayah, and is dedicated to her cause.</string>
    <string name="shen">Shen - The Eye Of Twilight</string>
    <string name="shen_sum">Among the secretive, Ionian warriors known as the Kinkou, Shen serves as their leader, the Eye of Twilight. He longs to remain free from the confusion of emotion, prejudice, and ego, and walks the unseen path of dispassionate judgment between the spirit realm and the physical world. Tasked with enforcing the equilibrium between them, Shen wields blades of steel and arcane energy against any who would threaten it.</string>
    <string name="yasuo">Yasuo - The Unforgiven</string>
    <string name="yasuo_sum">An Ionian of deep resolve, Yasuo is an agile swordsman who wields the air itself against his enemies. As a proud young man, he was falsely accused of murdering his master—unable to prove his innocence, he was forced to slay his own brother in self defense. Even after his master\'s true killer was revealed, Yasuo still could not forgive himself for all he had done, and now wanders his homeland with only the wind to guide his blade.</string>
    <string name="zed">Zed - The Master Of Shadows</string>
    <string name="zed_sum">Utterly ruthless and without mercy, Zed is the leader of the Order of Shadow, an organization he created with the intent of militarizing Ionia\'s magical and martial traditions to drive out Noxian invaders. During the war, desperation led him to unlock the secret shadow form—a malevolent spirit magic as dangerous and corrupting as it is powerful. Zed has mastered all of these forbidden techniques to destroy anything he sees as a threat to his nation, or his new order.</string>
    <string name="role">Role: %s</string>
    <string name="fighter">Fighter</string>
    <string name="tanker">Tanker</string>
    <string name="marksman">Marksman</string>
    <string name="mage">Mage</string>
    <string name="support">Support</string>
    <string name="assassin">Assassin</string>
</resources>